<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<description>CSH for Import module</description>
		<type>CSH</type>
		<csh_table>_MOD_txcategoriesMain_txcategoriesFunc</csh_table>
		<fileId>EXT:categories/locallang_csh_importmodule.xml</fileId>
		<labelContext type="array">
			<label index=".alttitle"></label>
		</labelContext>		
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index=".alttitle">The IPSV</label>		
			<label index="whatistheipsv.alttitle">About</label>
			<label index="whatistheipsv.description"><![CDATA[
The Integrated Public Sector Vocabulary (IPSV) is a structured list of terms for the Subject 
metadata of public sector resources.  Use of the IPSV is part of the compliance requirements 
for the e-Government Metadata Standard.   
 
The IPSV was formed from three taxonomies: the Government Category List (GCL), which 
was owned by the Cabinet Office, the Local Government Category List (LGCL), owned by 
esd-toolkit, and the seamlessUK taxonomy, owned by Essex County Council.  The IPSV’s 
detailed coverage of community information and local authority services reflects the focus of 
the latter two parent taxonomies.

The IPSV contains about 8000 terms and is used largely by public 
sector websites in Britain. 

Read more about the IPSV at: http://www.esd.org.uk/standards/ipsv/

			]]></label>
			<label index="pathtocsvfile.alttitle">Path to csv-file</label>	
			<label index="pathtocsvfile.description"><![CDATA[
			Path on the server where import-file can be found. 
			Use 'EXT:' to specify a path inside an extension.
			]]></label>
			<label index="prefixoriginalid.alttitle">Prefix original id</label>	
			<label index="prefixoriginalid.description"><![CDATA[
			The original id of the category will be prefixed with this string and stored with the record.
			]]></label>
			<label index="action.alttitle">Action</label>	
			<label index="action.description"><![CDATA[
			Determines which kind of action should be performed.
			
			Select <b>Import</b> if a clean import should be performed.
			
			Select <b>Update</b> if you already did an import and only want to update the records. The script will check if a record already exists in this path before it creates a new one. 
			]]></label>			
		</languageKey>
	</data>
	<orig_hash type="array">

	</orig_hash>	
</T3locallang>